raidrive.com 2019-08-24

# Privacy Policy

    Privacy Policy
    Last modified: 2019-04-21
    
    This Privacy Policy describes how Openboxlab and its affiliates ("RaiDrive," "we," "our" or "us") collect, use, and share information in connection with your use of our websites (including www.raidrive.com), services, and applications (collectively, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") does not apply to information our customers may process when using our Services.
    We may collect and receive information about users of our Services ("users," "you," or "your") from various sources, including: (i) information you provide through your license on the Services (your "Account") if you register for the Services; (ii) your use of the Services; and (iii) from third-party websites, services, and partners.
    We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or RaiDrive data collection, use, and disclosure practices, please contact us at support@raidrive.com.
    
    Information You provided:
    1. Registration. When you activate RaiDrive, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name and email address. We also collect information about RaiDrive license activations for the purposes of advertising promotions and licensing enforcement.
    2. Payment Information. When you purchase a license or subscription in our online store your financial account information is directed to our third-party payment processor. We do not store your financial account information on our systems
    3. Communications. If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide. We may also receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.
    
    Information We collect when you use our application:
    1. Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies. As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. In addition, when you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device.  This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to record your preferences.
    
    We do not collect the usernames, passwords, server names and drive-configuration settings in our software nor is any of this info transmitted to Openboxlab.
    What do we do with the information we collect?:
    We will use contact information to email purchase receipts, software update notifications, security update notifications as well as a few helpful emails to get started with the software. We also may occasionally send out a promotional email. Nothing more than once per month and all promotional emails will have a link allowing to opt-out of all future emails.
    
    Disclosure
    We won't disclose your email address, or other personal information, to anyone unless we reasonably believe it is necessary to comply with a subpoena, court order, law, or regulation we may disclose your personal information or file data to the extent required to fulfill our legal obligation.
    
    Security
    All personal information is collected via https secure communication and is kept in a secure database that is not subject to any unauthorized usage. We employ a variety of security technologies and measures designed to protect information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. However, please bear in mind that the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
    
    Data Retention
    We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).
    When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
    
    Business transfer
    If RaiDrive is involved in a business acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, or bankruptcy then your personal information may be transferred as part of the restructuring. We promise that either the acquiring institution will respect your personal information and file data in accordance with this privacy policy, or that you will be given the opportunity to opt-out of the transfer.
    
    Changes to this Privacy Policy
    Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our websites. If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through our Services, we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication.
    
    Contact Us
    If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at support@raidrive.com.

* * *
